## CHAIYONG RAGKHITWETSAGUL

CREST, Department of Computer Science University College London, Gower Street, London, UK ucabagk@ucl.ac.uk

# **PERSONAL PROFILE**

I am currently a 3rd-year PhD student in the Centre for Research on Evolution, Search and Testing (CREST), Department of Computer Science, University College London. I am also an assistant instructor at the Faculty of ICT, Mahidol University who is the main sponsor for my PhD study.

## **CURRENT PROJECTS**

ISiCS: Internet-scaled similar code search

Cloverflow: Study of outdated code and license violation of online clones between

Stack Overflow and open source projects A comparison of code similarity analysers

Optimising configurations of code clone detection tools

- PUBLICATIONS C. Ragkhitwetsagul, J. Krinke, D.Clark (2017). A Comparison of Code Similarity Analysers. Research Notes No. RN/17/04, 2017. University College London, UK
  - C. Ragkhitwetsagul, J. Krinke (2017). Using Compilation/Decompilation to Enhance Clone Detection. In 11th International Workshop on Software Clones, 2017. Klagenfurt, Austria, To Appear – The People's Choice Award
  - C. Ragkhitwetsagul, M. Paixao, M. Adham, S. Busari, J. Krinke, and J. H. Drake (2016). Searching for Configurations in Clone Evalution: A Replication Study. In 8th International Symposium on Search-based Software Engineering (SSBSE): Challenge Track, 2016. Raleigh, NC, USA. (NSF Student Travel Support)
  - C. Ragkhitwetsagul, J. Krinke, D. Clark (2016). Similarity of Source Code in the Presence of Pervasive Modifications. In 16th IEEE International Working Conference on Source Code Analysis and Manipulation (SCAM), 2016. Raleigh, NC, USA.
  - C. Ragkhitwetsagul (2016). Measuring Code Similarity in Large-scaled Code Corpora. In 32nd International Conference on Software Maintenance and Evolution (ICSME): Doctoral Symposium, 2016. Raleigh, NC, USA.
  - P. Janviriya, T. Ongarjithichai, P. Numruktrakul, C. Ragkhitwetsagul. (2014). Cloudy-Days: Cloud Storage Integration System. In ICT-ISPC 2014 (pp. 125-128). Nakhonpathom, Thailand.
  - P. Hathaiwichian, L. Siriwittayacharoen, A. Wongwachirawanich, C. Ragkhitwetsagul (2014). Android Application for Event Management and Information Propagation. In ICT-ISPC 2014 (pp. 139-142). Nakhonpathom, Thailand.

# **EDUCATION**

## 2014 - Present, PhD

# PhD in Computer Science

University College London, UK

Research topic: Code similarity and its applications to Internet-scaled code cloning Supervisors: Dr. Jens Krinke, Dr. David Clark

Research interest: code clone/plagiarism detection, code similarity, mining of software repositories, search-based software engineering

2007 - 2008, Master

Master of Science in IT - Very Large Information Systems

Carnegie Mellon University, USA

Capstone project: Honeydew - Meeting date prediction using machine learning

2002 – 2005, Undergraduate

Bachelor Degree in Computer Engineering (Magna cum Laude)

Kasetsart University, Thailand

**AWARDS** The People's Choice Award

2017

Using Compilation/Decompilation to Enhance Clone Detection

IWSC 2017. Klagenfurt, Austria.

NSF Student Travel Support (700 USD)

2016

SSBSE 2016. Raleigh, NC, USA.

2016

Microsoft Azure Research Award (20,000 USD)

ISiCS: Internet-scaled Similar Code Search project

Full PhD scholarship

2014 -2018

Mahidol University Academic Development Scholarship & Faculty of ICT, Mahidol University Scholarship

Best Project Award: 15-637 Web App Development,

2008

Carnegie Mellon University

Whimsy Word: multi-player online hangman game

Full Master degree scholarship

2007 - 2008

The Royal Thai Government scholarship

Winner of the 8th National Software Contest of Thailand (NSC)

DTAC & NOKIA i-Awards mobile app contest: finalists

2006

 ${\bf Category-Software\ for\ Entertainment}$ 

Sword Edge: virtual reality fighting game

2005

Interactive e-cards mobile application

EXPERIENCE

Research Student

Sep 2014 – Present

Centre for Research on Evolution, Search and Testing (CREST),

Software Systems Engineering (SSE) group,

Department of Computer Science, University College London

Conducting research in code similarity, code reuse, code clone/plagiarism detection, and search-based software engineering

Assistant Instructor

Dec 2012 - Sep 2014

Faculty of ICT, Mahidol University, Nakhonpathom, Thailand

Lectured Fundamentals of Programming, OOP, DBMS, Knowledge-based Systems, and Mobile App Development.

Advised three undergraduate student projects.

Consultant

Nov 2011 - Sep 2014

Blaccess Thailand

Made key decisions and providing company's vision.

Planned and managed IT projects and staffs.

System Analyst

Jan 2009 - Nov 2012

National Economic and Social Development Board, Thailand

Planned, migrated, and developed NESDB IT services (email systems, web applica-

tions, DBMS, and computer networks).

Administrated the NESDB applications and computer networks.

Teacher Feb 2010 - Dec 2012

## ProGaming, Thailand

Instructed Pro Android course on how to develop Android applications.

Instructed Pro iOS course on how to develop iOS applications.

Developer Jan 2009 - Dec 2012

## Kasetsart University, Thailand

Developed a digital repository, and training/project tracking system for Puparn Royal Development Study Center.

 ${\rm Mar}~2008$  -  ${\rm Aug}~2008$ In tern

## Oracle, USA

Developed of a new version of Oracle's internal testing platform, Distributed Testing System (DTS) 2.0, using Java web technology and Javascript.

Software Test Engineer

Feb 2006 - Apr 2007

## Microsoft, Thailand

Created automated test tools for testing localized versions of Windows Vista User Assistance Platform.

Tested user assistance (UA) contents in XML format.

**SKILLS** Platforms: macOS, Linux, Windows, Raspberry Pi, iOS, Android

Programming languages: Shell scripts, Java, C/C++, Obj-C, SQL, .Net, HTML,

PHP

	Subreviewer: REVE'17	Jun 2017
ACTIVITIES	Reviewer: STVR	Arp 2017
	Subreviewer: ICSME'17	Apr 2017
	Subreviewer: MSR'17	Feb 2017
	Subreviewer: IWSC'17	Dec 2016
	Subreviewer: SANER'17	Oct 2016
	Subreviewer: SCAM'16	Jul 2016

Reviewer: PeerJ Computer Science journal May 2016Jul 2015 Subreviewer: SCAM'15

REFERENCES References upon request.